drjudithorloff.com 2019-01-22

# 

                            Privacy Policy of ​drjudithorloff.com
This website collects some Personal Data from its Users.
Owner and Data Controller
Judith Orloff M.D.
1551 Ocean Ave., Suite 230
Santa Monica, CA 90401
Owner contact email:​ ​judith@judithorloff.com
Types of Data collected
Among the types of Personal Data that this Website collects, by itself or through third parties, there are:
Cookies, Usage Data, first name, last name, phone number, country, email address and city.
Complete details on each type of Personal Data collected are provided in the dedicated sections of this
privacy policy or by specific explanation texts displayed prior to the Data collection.
Personal Data may be freely provided by the User, or, in case of Usage Data, collected automatically
when using this Website.
Unless specified otherwise, all Data requested by this Website is mandatory and failure to provide this
Data may make it impossible for this Website to provide its services. In cases where this Website
specifically states that some Data is not mandatory, Users are free not to communicate this Data without
consequences to the availability or the functioning of the Service.
Users who are uncertain about which Personal Data is mandatory are welcome to contact the Owner.
Any use of Cookies – or of other tracking tools – by this Website or by the owners of third-party services
used by this Website serves the purpose of providing the Service required by the User, in addition to any
other purposes described in the present document and in the Cookie Policy, if available.
Users are responsible for any third-party Personal Data obtained, published or shared through this
Website and confirm that they have the third party's consent to provide the Data to the Owner.
Mode and place of processing the Data
Methods of processing
The Owner takes appropriate security measures to prevent unauthorized access, disclosure, modification,
or unauthorized destruction of the Data.

The Data processing is carried out using computers and/or IT enabled tools, following organizational
procedures and modes strictly related to the purposes indicated. In addition to the Owner, in some cases,
the Data may be accessible to certain types of persons in charge, involved with the operation of this
Website (administration, sales, marketing, legal, system administration) or external parties (such as
third-party technical service providers, mail carriers, hosting providers, IT companies, communications
agencies) appointed, if necessary, as Data Processors by the Owner. The updated list of these parties
may be requested from the Owner at any time.
Legal basis of processing
The Owner may process Personal Data relating to Users if one of the following applies:
      · Users have given their consent for one or more specific purposes. Note: Under some legislations
      the Owner may be allowed to process Personal Data until the User objects to such processing
      (“opt-out”), without having to rely on consent or any other of the following legal bases. This,
      however, does not apply, whenever the processing of Personal Data is subject to European data
      protection law;
      · provision of Data is necessary for the performance of an agreement with the User and/or for any
      pre-contractual obligations thereof;
      · processing is necessary for compliance with a legal obligation to which the Owner is subject;
      · processing is related to a task that is carried out in the public interest or in the exercise of official
      authority vested in the Owner;
      · processing is necessary for the purposes of the legitimate interests pursued by the Owner or by a
      third party.
In any case, the Owner will gladly help to clarify the specific legal basis that applies to the processing, and
in particular whether the provision of Personal Data is a statutory or contractual requirement, or a
requirement necessary to enter into a contract.
Place
The Data is processed at the Owner's operating offices and in any other places where the parties
involved in the processing are located.
Depending on the User's location, data transfers may involve transferring the User's Data to a country
other than their own. To find out more about the place of processing of such transferred Data, Users can
check the section containing details about the processing of Personal Data.
Users are also entitled to learn about the legal basis of Data transfers to a country outside the European
Union or to any international organization governed by public international law or set up by two or more
countries, such as the UN, and about the security measures taken by the Owner to safeguard their Data.
If any such transfer takes place, Users can find out more by checking the relevant sections of this
document or inquire with the Owner using the information provided in the contact section.

Retention time
Personal Data shall be processed and stored for as long as required by the purpose they have been
collected for.
Therefore:
      · Personal Data collected for purposes related to the performance of a contract between the Owner
      and the User shall be retained until such contract has been fully performed.
      · Personal Data collected for the purposes of the Owner’s legitimate interests shall be retained as
      long as needed to fulfill such purposes. Users may find specific information regarding the legitimate
      interests pursued by the Owner within the relevant sections of this document or by contacting the
      Owner.
The Owner may be allowed to retain Personal Data for a longer period whenever the User has given
consent to such processing, as long as such consent is not withdrawn. Furthermore, the Owner may be
obliged to retain Personal Data for a longer period whenever required to do so for the performance of a
legal obligation or upon order of an authority.
Once the retention period expires, Personal Data shall be deleted. Therefore, the right to access, the right
to erasure, the right to rectification and the right to data portability cannot be enforced after expiration of
the retention period.
The purposes of processing
The Data concerning the User is collected to allow the Owner to provide its Services, as well as for the
following purposes: Analytics, Contacting the User and Interaction with external social networks and
platforms.
Users can find further detailed information about such purposes of processing and about the specific
Personal Data used for each purpose in the respective sections of this document.
Detailed information on the processing of Personal Data
Personal Data is collected for the following purposes and using the following services:
Analytics
The services contained in this section enable the Owner to monitor and analyze web traffic and can be
used to keep track of User behavior.
Google Analytics (Google Inc.)
Google Analytics is a web analysis service provided by Google Inc. (“Google”). Google utilizes the Data
collected to track and examine the use of this Website, to prepare reports on its activities and share them
with other Google services.
Google may use the Data collected to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising
network.

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.
Place of processing: United States – ​Privacy Policy​ – ​Opt Out​. Privacy Shield participant.
Interaction with external social networks and platforms
This type of service allows interaction with social networks or other external platforms directly from the
pages of this Website.
The interaction and information obtained through this Website are always subject to the User’s privacy
settings for each social network.
This type of service might still collect traffic data for the pages where the service is installed, even when
Users do not use it.
LinkedIn button and social widgets (LinkedIn Corporation)
The LinkedIn button and social widgets are services allowing interaction with the LinkedIn social network
provided by LinkedIn Corporation.
Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.
Place of processing: United States – ​Privacy Policy​.
Facebook Like button and social widgets (Facebook, Inc.)
The Facebook Like button and social widgets are services allowing interaction with the Facebook social
network provided by Facebook, Inc.
Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.
Place of processing: United States – ​Privacy Policy​. Privacy Shield participant.
Twitter Like button and social widgets (Twitter, Inc.)
The Twitter Tweet button and social widgets are services allowing interaction with the Twitter social
network provided by Twitter, Inc.
Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.
Place of processing: United States – ​Privacy Policy​. Privacy Shield participant.
Pinterest “Pin it” button and social widgets (Pinterest)
The Pinterest “Pin it” button and social widgets are services allowing interaction with the Pinterest
platform provided by Pinterest Inc.
Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.
Place of processing: United States – ​Privacy Policy​.
Google+ +1 button and social widgets (Google Inc.)
The Google+ +1 button and social widgets are services allowing interaction with the Google+ social
network provided by Google Inc.
Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.
Place of processing: United States – ​Privacy Policy​. Privacy Shield participant.
YouTube button and social widgets (Google Inc.)
The YouTube button and social widgets are services allowing interaction with the YouTube social network
provided by Google Inc.
Personal Data collected: Usage Data.

Place of processing: United States – ​Privacy Policy​. Privacy Shield participant.
Instagram (Instagram, Inc.)
Instagram is an image visualization service provided by Instagram, Inc. that allows this Website to
incorporate content of this kind on its pages.
Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.
Place of processing: United States – ​Privacy Policy​.
Displaying content from external platforms
YouTube video widget (Google Inc.)
YouTube is a video content visualization
YouTube is a video content visualization service provided by Google Inc. that allows this Website to
incorporate content of this kind on its pages.
Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.
Place of processing: United States – ​Privacy Policy​. Privacy Shield participant.
Contacting the User
Contact form
By filling in the contact form with their Data, the User authorizes this Website to use these details to reply
to requests for information, quotes or any other kind of request as indicated by the form’s header.
Personal Data collected: city, country, email address, first name, last name and phone number.
The rights of Users
Users may exercise certain rights regarding their Data processed by the Owner.
In particular, Users have the right to do the following:
       · ​Withdraw their consent at any time.​ Users have the right to withdraw consent where they have
       previously given their consent to the processing of their Personal Data.
       · ​Object to processing of their Data.​ Users have the right to object to the processing of their
       Data if the processing is carried out on a legal basis other than consent. Further details are provided
       in the dedicated section below.
       · ​Access their Data.​ Users have the right to learn if Data is being processed by the Owner, obtain
       disclosure regarding certain aspects of the processing and obtain a copy of the Data undergoing
       processing.
       · ​Verify and seek rectification.​ Users have the right to verify the accuracy of their Data and ask
       for it to be updated or corrected.
       · ​Restrict the processing of their Data.​ Users have the right, under certain circumstances, to
       restrict the processing of their Data. In this case, the Owner will not process their Data for any
       purpose other than storing it.

      · ​Have their Personal Data deleted or otherwise removed.​ Users have the right, under certain
      circumstances, to obtain the erasure of their Data from the Owner.
      · ​Receive their Data and have it transferred to another controller.​ Users have the right to
      receive their Data in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format and, if technically
      feasible, to have it transmitted to another controller without any hindrance. This provision is
      applicable provided that the Data is processed by automated means and that the processing is
      based on the User's consent, on a contract which the User is part of or on pre-contractual
      obligations thereof.
      · ​Lodge a complaint.​ Users have the right to bring a claim before their competent data protection
      authority.
Details about the right to object to processing
Where Personal Data is processed for a public interest, in the exercise of an official authority vested in
the Owner or for the purposes of the legitimate interests pursued by the Owner, Users may object to such
processing by providing a ground related to their particular situation to justify the objection.
Users must know that, however, should their Personal Data be processed for direct marketing purposes,
they can object to that processing at any time without providing any justification. To learn, whether the
Owner is processing Personal Data for direct marketing purposes, Users may refer to the relevant
sections of this document.
How to exercise these rights
Any requests to exercise User rights can be directed to the Owner through the contact details provided in
this document. These requests can be exercised free of charge and will be addressed by the Owner as
early as possible and always within one month.
Additional information about Data collection and processing
Legal action
The User's Personal Data may be used for legal purposes by the Owner in Court or in the stages leading
to possible legal action arising from improper use of this Website or the related Services.
The User declares to be aware that the Owner may be required to reveal personal data upon request of
public authorities.
Additional information about User's Personal Data
In addition to the information contained in this privacy policy, this Website may provide the User with
additional and contextual information concerning particular Services or the collection and processing of
Personal Data upon request.

 System logs and maintenance
 For operation and maintenance purposes, this Website and any third-party services may collect files that
 record interaction with this Website (System logs) use other Personal Data (such as the IP Address) for
 this purpose.
 Information not contained in this policy
 More details concerning the collection or processing of Personal Data may be requested from the Owner
 at any time. Please see the contact information at the beginning of this document.
 How “Do Not Track” requests are handled
 This Website does not support “Do Not Track” requests.
 To determine whether any of the third-party services it uses honor the “Do Not Track” requests, please
 read their privacy policies.
 Changes to this privacy policy
 The Owner reserves the right to make changes to this privacy policy at any time by giving notice to its
 Users on this page and possibly within this Website and/or - as far as technically and legally feasible -
 sending a notice to Users via any contact information available to the Owner. It is strongly recommended
 to check this page often, referring to the date of the last modification listed at the bottom.
 Should the changes affect processing activities performed on the basis of the User’s consent, the Owner
 shall collect new consent from the User, where required.
Definitions and legal references
 Personal Data (or Data)
 Any information that directly, indirectly, or in connection with other information — including a personal
 identification number — allows for the identification or identifiability of a natural person.
 Usage Data
 Information collected automatically through this Website (or third-party services employed in this
 Website), which can include: the IP addresses or domain names of the computers utilized by the Users
 who use this Website, the URI addresses (Uniform Resource Identifier), the time of the request, the
 method utilized to submit the request to the server, the size of the file received in response, the numerical
 code indicating the status of the server's answer (successful outcome, error, etc.), the country of origin,
 the features of the browser and the operating system utilized by the User, the various time details per visit
 (e.g., the time spent on each page within the Website) and the details about the path followed within the
 Website with special reference to the sequence of pages visited, and other parameters about the device
 operating system and/or the User's IT environment.

User
The individual using this Website who, unless otherwise specified, coincides with the Data Subject.
Data Subject
The natural person to whom the Personal Data refers.
Data Processor (or Data Supervisor)
The natural or legal person, public authority, agency or other body which processes Personal Data on
behalf of the Controller, as described in this privacy policy.
Data Controller (or Owner)
The natural or legal person, public authority, agency or other body which, alone or jointly with others,
determines the purposes and means of the processing of Personal Data, including the security measures
concerning the operation and use of this Website. The Data Controller, unless otherwise specified, is the
Owner of this Website.
This Website
The means by which the Personal Data of the User is collected and processed.
Service
The service provided by this Website as described in the relative terms (if available) and on this
site/website.
European Union (or EU)
Unless otherwise specified, all references made within this document to the European Union include all
current member states to the European Union and the European Economic Area.
Cookies
Small sets of data stored in the User's device.
Legal information
This privacy statement has been prepared based on provisions of multiple legislations, including Art.
13/14 of Regulation (EU) 2016/679 (General Data Protection Regulation).
This privacy policy relates solely to this Website, if not stated otherwise within this document.
